<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Novels Archives - Book Readus</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 13:09:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9</generator>

<image>
	<url>./../../../wp-content/uploads/2022/03/cropped-favicon-1-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Novels Archives - Book Readus</title>
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Om Swami: As we know him</title>
		<link>./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/om-swami-as-we-know-him/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/om-swami-as-we-know-him/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mdfarzan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 06:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
<li class="ms-pt-xs sku ng-binding ng-scope" data-ng-if="product.sku"><b class="ng-binding">SKU</b>: OSAWKMIT77</li>
<li class="ms-pt-xs brand-name ms-pb-xs ng-binding ng-scope" data-ng-if="product.brand"><b class="ng-binding">BRAND</b>: ISMITA TANDON</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/om-swami-as-we-know-him/index.html">Om Swami: As we know him</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="./../../../index.html">Book Readus</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything I thought to be true about life, its meaning was challenged after meeting Swami. It was reduced to dust. Soon I had to admit that there were things far beyond the scope of my rational mind.&#8217; What is it that draws one to a mystic? What is it like to know at close quarters a man whose powers are beyond the conscious mind? What does it feel like to be fulfilled spiritually, to feel understood, to stand revealed? As Ismita Tandon and Swami Vidyananda Om explore their feelings for Om Swami, their baffling experiences with him, a secret world of mystical phenomena lights up. They talk about the intimacy of their daily lives with Swami, observing his sheer power, his simplicity, his empathy for every living creature he encounters and the care with which he chooses every word he speaks, no matter how big or small the matter. They speak of his beauty, his divinity. What emerges is a moving portrait of devotion and trust, and the startling image of a saint who was able to inspire such depth of feeling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/om-swami-as-we-know-him/index.html">Om Swami: As we know him</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="./../../../index.html">Book Readus</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/om-swami-as-we-know-him/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets by J. K. Rowling</title>
		<link>./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/harry-potter-and-the-chamber-of-secrets-by-j-k-rowling/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/harry-potter-and-the-chamber-of-secrets-by-j-k-rowling/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mdfarzan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?post_type=product&#038;p=48</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ever since Harry Potter had come home for the summer, the Dursleys had been so mean and hideous that all Harry wanted was to get back to the Hogwarts School for Witchcraft and Wizardry. But just as hes packing his bags, Harry receives a warning from a strange, impish creature who says that if Harry returns to Hogwarts, disaster will strike. And strike it does...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/harry-potter-and-the-chamber-of-secrets-by-j-k-rowling/index.html">Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets by J. K. Rowling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="./../../../index.html">Book Readus</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ever since Harry Potter had come home for the summer, the Dursleys had been so mean and hideous that all Harry wanted was to get back to the Hogwarts School for Witchcraft and Wizardry. But just as hes packing his bags, Harry receives a warning from a strange, impish creature who says that if Harry returns to Hogwarts, disaster will strike. And strike it does. For in Harry Ever since Harry Potter had come home for the summer, the Dursleys had been so mean and hideous that all Harry wanted was to get back to the Hogwarts School for Witchcraft and Wizardry. But just as hes packing his bags, Harry receives a warning from a strange, impish creature who says that if Harry returns to Hogwarts, disaster will strike. And strike it does. For in Harrys second year at Hogwarts, fresh torments and horrors arise, including an outrageously stuck-up new professor and a spirit who haunts the girls bathroom. But then the real trouble begins &#8212; someone is turning Hogwarts students to stone. Could it be Draco Malfoy, a more poisonous rival than ever? Could it possibly be Hagrid, whose mysterious past is finally told? Or could it be the one everyone at Hogwarts most suspects&#8230;Harry Potter himself!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/harry-potter-and-the-chamber-of-secrets-by-j-k-rowling/index.html">Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets by J. K. Rowling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="./../../../index.html">Book Readus</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../shop/non-fiction/biography/harry-potter-and-the-chamber-of-secrets-by-j-k-rowling/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
